



Troels Zink Kristensen

Born: April 30th, 1997

Address: Niels Bohrs Allé 23, 01,

-3114. 5230 Odense M

E-mail: T.Zink.Business@outlook.com

Phone: +45 61 28 58 32

About me

Denmark in Odense.

My name is Troels Zink Kristensen, and I am currently 22 years old. I live in Odense but lived in Varde Kommune in Western Jutland until 2017. I started working at 13 years old, and since then I have worked most of the time, except in recent years during my education. I long for a job alongside my study. I am currently studying Civil Engineering in Robot Technology at University of Southern

I am dedicated and always meet on time. I give all that I have during work, and often more than that. I have never had any sick days. A recommendation from my former boss can be acquired at my LinkedIn-profile.



Education

2012 - 2013

Breininggaard continuation school.

2013 - 2016

HTX in Esbjerg.

Study programme: Mathematics, IT, programming.

Grade point average: 11.4

2016 - 2017

Gap year.

Went to India, Nepal and Thailand for around two months.

2017 - 2022

Civil Engineering in Robot Technology, SDU Odense. Currently at 6th semester.



Programming skills

C++	000	Assembler	000
С	000	VHDL	000
	000		000

C#	000	MATLAB	000
РНР	000	HTML/CSS	000

IP	∞	HTML/CSS	∞

Python	∞	MySQL	00
Javascript		PLC	00



Work experience

2010 – 2012 | Floor sweeper | Lunde Maskincenter

Sweeping, vacuum cleaning, overall cleaning.

2013 – 2015 | Youth worker | Fakta in Ølgod

Operating the check-out desk, customer service, cleaning, refilling shelves.

2015 - 2017 | 'Nøglebærer' | Fakta in Ølgod

During daytime: Equivalent to youth worker. During nighttime: Responsibility for the supermarket, responsibility for a youth worker, checking dates on food, refilling shelves, cleaning, amongst other things.

2018 - 2019 | Technician | PhoneCare

Responsibility for a shop. Worked in Odense, Kolding, Slagelse and Copenhagen. Consisted of repairment of smartphones, customer service and cleaning.

2020 | Instructor | SDU in Odense

Teaching students at 2nd semester on my education in object-oriented programming (C++).

2020 | Bachelor thesis | Inwatec

Improving the success rate of a robot's gripper by detecting keypoints using computer vision and Al.



Languages

Danish



